womenfreebies.ca 2014-02-20

# WomenFreebies.ca | Privacy

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy... 

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 
  * To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) 
  * To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. 
  * To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. 

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe (OPT OUT) from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe (OPT OUT) instructions at the bottom of each email. 

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

## Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information 

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service. 

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. 

## Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy. 

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

1338 Wellington Street West, Unit 200  
Ottawa, ON K1Y 3B7  
Canada

Email: [sarah@womenfreebies.ca](mailto:sarah@womenfreebies.ca)  
Phone: (613) 592-6642
